[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "Did you imagine ever working for him?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "This inner intensity that I have tended to, in some ways, be destructive.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "But who's the real Newt Gingrich?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's fun.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Why here?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Any super PAC.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Yours?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Any.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Yours or Mitt Romney's secret super PAC?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It's not a question about being Saint Newt, it's a question about where you're prepared to fight.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "So where did Saint Newt come from?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, probably I would have reacted earlier to the attack ads, especially the ones that were untrue.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "If you'd known what was coming?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I like the brilliant visionary part.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What's your response to that?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's part of what I have to overcome.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "ORGAN: In answer to the too much baggage and the erratic allegations, I mean a bit of truth of both, I would say, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, the point is, if a guy is running for president -- he has two major credentials, his record as governor which he doesn't want to talk about because he was much more liberal as governor than a Republican primary will ever endorse.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "But he makes that assertion anyway.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "But if he manages to establish that his record at Bain was such that he created more jobs than he effectively lost you could argue that's exactly what is needed in America right now in the sense that you're going to have to cut, aren't you?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, I think we've certainly raised the question -- it's not about capitalism, it's not about free enterprise, it's about values, character and judgment.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "-- he was a force for negative?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What do you actually think of him personally as a man?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "No, I have no view.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "You have no view?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "He is a competitor.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Do you like him?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I'm only saying --", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "You don't have to go to the sun to know it's hot, do you?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I still stand by the fact that he is -- that he is not truthful.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Do you still stand by the fact he's a liar about you?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I don't have an obligation to answer any of that.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What do you think of his character?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "If somebody -- first of all, you had a fairly long career.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Is it better for a leader, for a potential president of the United States, to admit that they have been wrong and to change their mind about issues, or to stick stubbornly by their same platform on these things decade after decade?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "I mean, it would be strange if you hadn't, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, if you go to Romneytaxes.com you'll see every single tax he raised while he's governor.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "But are you dubious about Mitt Romney's motivation for changing his position?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Could you imagine ever working for him?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Can there be a good result?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "If you don't win, given you've set that parameter, do you drop out?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I'm not saying it's his fault or not his fault.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Or is that just good politics?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Yes, I think politically, this -- well, it's the most decisive week.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is this the biggest week of your life politically?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Is Rick Santorum -- he had the Santorum surge, took a bit of a hit in New Hampshire, not necessarily surprisingly, but is it over for him, or do you think you continue to see him get traction?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, that's his decision.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Are you surprised Governor Perry is still going?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "No, never --", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "At what point does the party have to rally, as you say, behind this one consensus?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "The party never has to rally.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Has it reached that point now?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "But doesn't it have to -- doesn't it have to collectively say, \"We're now going to have these two duke it out\"?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "But that is not the party's function.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Does it help that you have endless candidates carrying on?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, there were two decisions.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Given what you experienced on those battlefields, given what you saw, if you had been the commander-in-chief, that decision about Iraq, would have taken that decision?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, I'm looking with foresight.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "You mean with hindsight or without hindsight?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, by then you've already been pushed into a corner where only military action is capable.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "And what would do in that circumstance?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I would say it would be to protect the interests of America and her allies, and to do it in as effective a way as possible with the minimum of force and the minimum of risk.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "If I said to you, give me a phrase which would sum up your kind of overview of a modern American foreign policy, what would you say it would be?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "No, not much.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Would you quibble with any of those comparisons?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Why is this not possible now?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I think it's the whole system.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Not Republicans?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I love the capacity of Washington pundits to be -- to be sort of serially wrong, you know.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Do they underestimate you?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "If you were in South Carolina and you're thinking \"should I vote for this guy,\" what is the biggest misconception about you personally?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Extraordinarily.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How important is your wife to you?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Oh, sure.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Are you as happy with Callista as you've ever been with any woman in your life?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Look, I think people have every right to ask of any presidential candidate virtually everything.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Do you accept it's a valid criticism?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "There is a power to the Eucharist in the Catholic tradition that is a power to -- the community -- one of the things that the people would say to me is welcome home.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "How has that changed you as a person?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Well, I think that that's something that Romney has to be able to explain.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "No, I'm not judgmental about how people go to God.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Do you as a Catholic find it strange?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "If I could be any animal?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "An elephant?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "They have 105,000 muscles in their trunk.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "And they're big and they last a long time.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You want 105,000 muscles in your trunk?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I have no idea and I'm not going to go down that road.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What kind of animal do you think Mitt Romney would be?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "INGRICH: Well, I think first of all you have to offer an optimistic vision of a hopeful, successful American future.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "What are the key things that a new president come November, if it is a new president, needs to do?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, considering that he wrote from Korea after I did my very first newspaper article at 10.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "What do you think he would make of the Newt Gingrich that you've become?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Would he prefer the Newt Gingrich today to the one that he found slightly less favorite?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Oh, my mother would just love me.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "What would your mother make of you?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Yes, in a sense.", "docId": "120111pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Do you feel like you've almost spent the last 50 years bracing yourself for this week and this battle?", "qSentId": 606}]